What are you doing?
I'm making fish out of leaves.
Looking good.
This one's a fish, and this is an octopus.
Isn't that a starfish?
Hmm?
E-Excuse me.
Hall of
The Starfish -
The Book
Rin, do you want this?
A book about fish!
Fish Drawing Book
This one's a salmon! It's kinda salty!
You're interested in eating them?
Rin, look. It's a flounder.
Flounder?
It's a fish that has its eyes on the same side of its body.
You're right!
This one looks like a puffer fish, doesn't it?
Yeah, it does.
Look, Daikichi.
Cheating is bad.
What do you mean, cheating?
Cutting the leaves is considered cheating.
This isn't cheating. It's more like adult's intelligence.
Oh!
What should we do? It's all wrinkly.
There are holes in the acorns!
Holes?
Bugs, I suppose.
Ah, we had that happen here too.
When I told Reina that she wasn't allowed to bring acorns inside the house,
she threw a hissy fit.
What should we do? The acorns have bugs in them, and the leaves are all dry and wrinkly.
Leaves? We pressed them between books.
Pressed them?
I'm home!
Rin! Wash your hands first.
In a minute!
Daikichi, let's go!
Aquarium of leaves